[{"answer": "Would you let go of my arm?! I'm trying to drive, you're getting us both killed", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Trip-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Obviously we're gonna call the police and tell that he's not the guy", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "God, I'm starved, I'm weak from hunger", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Trip-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Time like what? I'm hungry. My stomach doesn't know that my friend's wanted", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Pay phone in L.A., look it's a miracle. CUT TO my friend SINGING IN A SHOWER FOLLOWED BY A FALLING SOUND BACK TO GEORGE AND JERRY ON THE STREE", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Trip-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "No, I don't have any change. I never carry change", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "I don't have any change. You've got any change", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Trip-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Well, we need change and all I have is twenties", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "You know, I haven't eaten anything", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Trip-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Why don't you just call 911", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Why don't you just call 911", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Trip-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Of course it is", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "But is this an emergency", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Trip-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "How is this an emergency", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "What's the matter with you? Are you crazy? Why are you using my name?", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Trip-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "What am I scared of? I'm scared of the same thing that you are, everything! Why don't you just use your own name", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Oh yeah. Yes I have some very important information regarding the smog strangler.  would you suck a mint or something. Can I come right now? I suppose, where are you located? Where is that? I don't know where we are. Where are we", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Trip-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "We don't know. He says ask somebody, ask that guy", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Excuse me Ms. which street are we on", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Trip-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "You don't know", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "I don't know", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Trip-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I don't know", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "You don't know", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Trip-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "How come you don't know what street are you on", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "I don't know", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Trip-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "You don't know", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Brutal", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Trip-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "I don't know, five bucks a night", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "What me? Fabulous, just fabulous. I've got a lot of auditions, a lot of call backs and I've got a lot of interest for my movie treatment. I'm in development, I'm in developed vehicles. And there's a lot of energy here, man. You know, the vibe, it's powerful. I'm just swept up at it. Yeah, I'm a player", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Trip-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Yeah, a player..", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Don't you ever swear to my God, my friend. My God is the god who protects the innocent and punishes the evil scum like you, have you got that", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Trip-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "No! You have made the mistake, my friend. Sickies like you always do. The only difference is that this time you're gonna pay", "qsentId": 32}]